http://www.cbtwaco.com/privacy-policy

Enroll
Forgot Password?
Contact Us
Trust Login
Enroll
Forgot Password?
Trust Login
Get the App
Login
All CB&T locations will be closed on Monday, October 12th in observance of the Columbus Day holiday.
All CB&T lobbies are closed to customer traffic. Normal hours remain for all Motor Banks and the Contact Center.
×
Username
Password
Enroll
Forgot Password?
Contact Us
Trust Login
Enroll
Forgot Password?
Trust Login
Forgot Password?
FACTS
WHAT DOES COMMUNITY BANK & TRUST DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
Account balances and payment history
Credit history and credit scores
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Community Bank & Trust chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does COMMUNITY BANK & TRUST Share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes
Such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes
to offer our products and services to you
No
We Don't Share
For joint marketing with other financial companies
No
We Don't Share
Questions?
Call (254) 753-1521 or go to www.cbtwaco.bank
More Information
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
COMMUNITY BANK & TRUST
What we do
How does COMMUNITY BANK & TRUST protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
We restrict access to your personal and account information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products and services to you.
How does COMMUNITY BANK & TRUST collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account or deposit money
Pay your bills or apply for a loan
Use your credit or debit card
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your credit worthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Our affiliates include others, such as The Community Company.
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Community Bank & Trust does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
COMMUNITY BANK & TRUST doesn’t jointly market
Other Important Information
Special Notice for Texas Residents
HOW TO FILE A COMPLAINT. We are chartered/licensed/registered under the laws of the state of Texas and by state law are subject to regulatory oversight by the Texas Department of Banking. Any consumer wishing to file a complaint against us should contact the Texas Department of Banking through one of the means indicated below:
In Person or U.S. Mail:
Texas Department of Banking
Consumer Assistance Activities
2601 North Lamar Boulevard, Suite 300
Austin, TX 78705-4294
Telephone No.: (877) 276-5554
Email: consumer.complaints@dob.texas.gov
Website: www.dob.texas.gov
Community Bank & Trust also engages in the money transmission and/or currency exchange business as an authorized delegate of Travelex Currency Services Inc. under Chapter 151 of the Texas Finance Code. If you have a complaint, first contact the consumer assistance division of Travelex Currency Services Inc. at 1-877-414-6359 (toll free), if you still have an unresolved complaint regarding the company's money transmission or currency exchange activity, please direct your complaint to the Texas Department of Banking.
Revised April 2018
Stay Connected
Receive our Newsletter to stay up to date!
